(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[Fate Chooses You]
[Episode 19]
Immortal, please remember
to keep composed, calm,
and concentrated all the time.
If you can't find the gate,
by no means should you force yourself.
Immortal,
have you found that person?
If not, just give up.
You've been in your spiritual sea
for a long time.
At this rate,
your divine sense will be damaged,
Immortal.
Get the basin here.
Let me feed him.
He will wake up
in another 4 hours.
If he experiences
any weakness in the limbs,
dizziness, or nausea,
consider it normal.
Feed him medicine every 4 hours.
Then he will recover in 3 to 5 days.
Three to five days?
Does it have to be that long?
A black sandstorm is happening outside.
I'd say it'll last
at least another day and night.
It's hard to determine exactly
how long it will last.
We can't go out anyway.
Might as well stay here for now.
Well...
I...
Who really are you?
My employers.
Didn't I tell you already?
Those immortal sect cultivators are
here to catch you, right?
I... well...
We don't know
any immortal sect cultivators
or what you're talking about.
Penniless though you are,
you hired Lord of Rust-Sword to escort you
along the way.
What are you afraid of?
Given Lord of Rust-Sword's personality,
he would definitely tell you
that he ranks
second on the List of Top Martial Artists.
When the mounted bandits appeared earlier,
you fled in panic
even before seeing them.
Then the young sect master
of Lingji Mountain showed up.
As you learned
he was chasing after a group
of demonic cultivators
who had stolen books,
why did you panic again?
I... I...
What should we do?
What...
are you people talking about?
Immortal.
Immortal!
It's time you woke up!
Immortal.
Immortal?
It's a success.
She found him.
Mr. Lu.
Mr. Lu?
Who is it?
Who's in there?
It's me, Xin Mei.
Where are you?
Who are you talking to?
I'm in your spiritual sea.
Mr. Lu,
please come meet me.
[Lu Qianqiao's spiritual sea]
What brings you to my spiritual sea?
I used the Spirit Projection Technique.
I traveled my spiritual sea
and found the gate leading to you.
That was how I reached here.
The Spirit Projection Technique?
There are thousands
of marks in your spiritual sea.
It's extremely difficult to locate
the gate leading to me.
How did you find it?
I'm not sure myself.
I just thought I'd give it a try.
At first, it was hard to identify
the right gate.
Nonetheless, a blood thread
in me came to my aid.
Following its guidance,
I finally found you.
You're a hybrid of War Demons
and the Human Race,
burdened with the Five Deficiencies Curse.
To get rid of the divine punishment
and reincarnate as a human,
you must pass 5 trials:
skin and flesh replacing, bone renewal,
blood purification, and heart alteration.
Each trial hangs by a thread
between life and death.
You must find a blood relative
to form a blood pact with you
and build a connection
in your spiritual sea,
so when you stand at death's door,
that bond may grant you a lifeline—
a chance to cheat death.
You have no family,
so you have to marry someone
to establish this blood pact.
Why did you come see me?
Don't you know
why I came see you,
Lord Lu Huai?
Miss,
here are the two cloaks you asked for.
What do you think?
Not bad.
Pack them up for me.
Sure.
Thank you.
Sir, do you know any
camel caravan
that is leaving the city soon?
Don't you see
a black sandstorm is approaching?
The wind is already picking up.
No camel caravan
will risk leaving the city.
They are all resting now.
How many days
will the sandstorm last?
Who would know?
When it ends, it ends.
[Tailor Shop]
Take care, miss.
That's the full account of events.
I didn't expect
to meet you again
in Chongling Valley.
So by the time
I woke up at the Safe Haven Inn,
I hadn't had a severe illness.
You had just erased my memories,
right?
Right.
I don't understand.
You have great powers.
In Chongling Valley,
even Cang Fengzi from Tianyuan Sect
was no match for you.
But back then,
why did you let yourself be imprisoned
and willingly die a death by 1,000 cuts?
Knowing full well
that you wouldn't perish,
why did you marry me at all?
Sorry.
I had my own reason to do so.
I just can't tell you why.
Although I learned
the truth afterwards,
I couldn't have done anything
to you since I was a mere
Foundation Establishment Stage cultivator.
Why did you have to
erase my memories?
Why did you continue to
keep me in the dark?
That was never my intention.
Meeting you again in Chongling Valley
was a pure accident.
I know
I've brought you much trouble.
Whatever compensation you want,
just name it.
I'll say yes.
But you just can't give me an explanation,
can you?
Fine.
Then let me ask you one last question.
Ask away.
Where are you at the moment?
Young Sect Master,
what's on your mind?
Something's wrong.
Something is really wrong.
What is wrong?
There's something odd about those people
around Lu Qianqiao.
Could they be
the demonic cultivators
who stole
from the Scripture Pavilion?
What makes you say so?
Previously, when I was talking
to Lu Qianqiao,
those people around him
looked very nervous.
They seemed sneaky
and suspicious.
Chongling Valley
has always been close to mortals.
Could Lu Qianqiao
be covering
for these people?
If that's true,
it'll be bad news.
Why?
Because we can't defeat him.
Are you silly or what?
We don't have to fight those people.
What we need to do
is to figure out their backgrounds first.
If our guess is proven correct,
we'll take them down directly.
There's no need to fear Lu Qianqiao,
since those people stole from us first.
We're in the right.
Let's go!
Young Sect Master Lin.
You seem to be in a hurry.
Where are you heading?
It's none of your business.
Get out of my way.
A bunch of mortals
managed to steal
from your precious library.
The immortal sects in the Central Plains
like yours are really getting better.
Have I been
too polite to you these days?
Catching a bunch of ordinary mortals
actually
requires action
from the young sect master.
Is everyone else
dead here in Lingji Mountain?
Seriously?
Is Jiang Ji also dead?
Lu,
what's with you?
Please say something.
The greatest form is without shape.
Drop!
You caused that incident at Bishui Branch.
After killing Hewabu,
instead of scurrying back
to the Central Plains,
you have the gall to stay in North Xiang.
You must have a death wish.
Did Zuo Yingying tell you that?
She means to set us
fighting against each other
so she can reap the benefits effortlessly.
Too bad
that she won't see it happen.
Because you will soon
be killed by me.
For a burly man,
your moves are quite gentle.
That wasn't a pleasant tune.
Don't you think so?
Cover your ears!
It's over.
You do have a few tricks up your sleeve.
Immortal,
you really found it?
How did you do that?
What are we going to do now?
Sheng.
Sheng!
Senior Sister,
I have to leave first
for an urgent matter.
You should hurry back too.
Try not to delay.
Sheng!
I finally found you.
A sandstorm is coming.
We can't leave the city.
-Where are we going?
Who are you looking for?
Run.
Run as far as you can!
Take them away.
Let's go.
I don't care what grudges you have
against each other.
I'll only ask one thing.
Are they
demonic cultivators from Wushuang Society?
I'll take your silence as yes。
Then I'm sorry.
I have to take
these people away today.
Who do you think you are?
You think you can do that
just because you say so?
Since we share the same goal,
why don't we team up?
Dharma King, you're great yourself.
Why join forces with others?
Even I dare not interfere.
Stop making sarcastic remarks.
If they get away,
the Master will hold you accountable.
Who are you?
I am Xia Xuanzi.
What enmity lies between us
that you seek my life?
Do you recognize this man?
I am his father.
I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to kill you!
I did kill him.
If I hadn't,
he would've taken my life.
Glad that you admitted it.
I'll kindly give you a quick death then.
Master, help!
I don't mean to give you a hard time.
But they stole from us,
so I have to
bring them back for a trial.
How dare you, a lapdog for immortal sects,
defile the dignity of the Phoenix God?
You'll be dead meat!
What an evil technique.
What did he just drink?
Spare us, Dharma King!
Please spare our lives!
Anything wrong?
You hold them off for a while.
But...
how do I do that?
Kill them.
Kill all of them!
Mr. Lu.
Leave this to me.
Mr. Lu!
Lu,
wake up!
What are you doing?
He's not the one I am after.
Plus, I know this person.
You can't kill him.
Young Sect Master,
should we keep on fighting?
Do we still want to catch them?
That can wait a bit.
You're at the Void Stage.
The Spirit Projection Technique.
You mere Nascent Soul cultivator,
who really are you?
Why not attack now?
Once he wakes up,
we'll stand no chance of winning!
How will that be?
Dharma King, you haven't used
your full strength yet.
If you do,
none of them can be match for you.
It is truly not easy for you,
a Nascent Soul cultivator, to have caused
this much damage to me.
What a shame
that you're only controlling
a Foundation Establishment Stage
cultivator's body.
Otherwise, things would be
a bit difficult for me.
It's time to put an end to all this!
Impressive.
So are you.
You have
extraordinary cultivation power.
The Foundation Establishment Stage focuses
on physical strength, not the spirit.
The Golden Core Stage focuses
on the spirit, not the heart.
The Nascent Soul Stage focuses
on the heart, not the energy.
Given that, cultivators at these stages
all have easily identified weak spots,
namely their heads and necks, hearts,
and energy bases.
When they reach the Void Stage,
their weak spots become veiled.
I can see that your breathing is steady
and your weaknesses are hidden.
I guess you have reached
the middle phase of the Void Stage.
You know quite a lot.
Not only that,
I'm also aware
that though there is one mere gap
between the middle
and top phases of the Void Stage,
it is utterly challenging to cross it.
The reason is
that towards the end of cultivation,
cultivators usually lack energy,
but have no way to replenish it.
Those who can't overcome this problem
will show their weak spots.
All is over now.
How did you figure that out?
♪ I ask the Nine Heavens:
what is the purpose of this life? ♪
♪ With my spine as my monument,
I shall never kneel ♪
♪ Though this life be wretched,
I will not sink so low ♪
♪ As to become a puppet of fate ♪
♪ Rather than bowing my back
to apologize to the Heavens ♪
♪ I would sooner rewrite
this fated calamity ♪
♪ I demand the story
follow my own desire ♪
♪ To serve as its final conclusion ♪
It's been a pleasure working with you.
Take them down.
Sir,
w-where are you taking me
to?
H-How about this?
Let's make a deal.
I'll leave with my men right away.
And I promise
I'll never mess with
your people again.
Agreed?
P-Please put me down now.
P-Please put me down!
Mr. Lu.
Don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
V-Vajra Xunmu,
I didn't see anything,
and I won't disclose anything.
Please spare my life.
From now on, I...
I will follow you wholeheartedly
and even risk my life for you
with absolute loyalty!
Really?
Really!
Then I'd love to have you prove
your loyalty with your life.
-Greetings, Vajra Xunmu.
Greetings, Master.
You're back.
I'm so useless
that I failed to save Dharma King Wenyin.
Who killed him?
The young sect master of Lingji Mountain,
son of Lin An,
Lin Muhan.
[The Crescent Lake]
Wipe your hands.
Thank you, Mr. Lu.
After our parting in Chongling Valley,
I've been having weird dreams
every now and then.
Everything that happens in these dreams
sometimes seems real, and sometimes fake.
It's vague and obscure.
All appears ethereal and disorderly.
But I always feel like I have
experienced everything in reality.
Suppose one's memories
stand for his or her entire life,
then I guess I have died once.
What exactly should I call you?
Are you Lu Huai,
the magistrate of Wei County,
or the Autumn Crimson Blade,
a hero from the martial arts world,
or...
My name is Lu Qianqiao.
"Qian" means thousands,
and "Qiao" means tall trees.
I've told you that.
Yes, you have.
You've said many words to me,
yet not all of them are real.
Should I even believe you?
I did lie to you.
Your anger is understandable.
But right now,
I have a very important task to do.
When I finish it,
I'll give you an explanation.
With that said, please trust me.
I have no intention of harming you.
Aside from erasing my memories,
are you hiding anything else
from me?
Good thing I didn't lose it.
It's a type of candy
made exclusively in North Xiang.
Have you tasted it?
No, never.
Then you can have this.
It's very sweet.
Give me the handkerchief.
I'll wash it.
Lu Qianqiao,
you are a War Demon, aren't you?
What are they doing?
How very baffling.
This is tamarind candy.
It tastes rather sour
without any sweetness.
You don't have a sense of taste,
do you?
You are a War Demon.
I should have thought of that earlier.
You didn't like to eat
when we were in Chongling Valley.
All you took in was liquor.
It's said that War Demons find everything
they eat tastes rotten.
Only the spiciness of liquor
can provide some relief.
Later on, upon hearing
about my erased memories,
I went to Wei County
and visited your residence.
You made all your paintings
with black ink only.
That's because War Demons
cannot tell colors at all.
Suffering the cruel death
by 1,000 cuts
causes severe damage even to a cultivator
at the Void Stage.
Yet it left no scar on you at all.
You healed unbelievably fast.
War Demons are endowed
with that ability too.
Given all that,
you erased my memories to prevent me
from figuring out your real identity.
War Demons
are bloodthirsty by nature.
Many years ago,
to build the heavenly ladder
and ripen the seed of Jianmu Tree,
you War Demons inflicted severe harm
on thousands of innocents.
If it hadn't been for the alliance
of immortal sects and the Youhu Clan,
the world would have
fallen under the rule of War Demons!
It has been
several decades since that brutal war.
Yet the smell of blood
on this land has not faded
after all these years!
The buried bones
of our ancestors in the ground
have not gone cold yet!
There is rage between our races,
and a blood debt of near annihilation!
Then what?
What do you want me to do?
Among the thousands of households
that the War Demons swept through
in hundreds of cities,
not even one in ten survived.
Back then, 24 immortal sects joined forces
to fight against the War Demons.
Half of these sects were destroyed.
At that time, there were
dozens of disciples in Xin Xie Manor.
In the end, I was the only one left.
With such feud in heart,
what do you expect me to do?
Lu Qianqiao, say something!
What do you want me to say?
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to snap your neck,
devour your flesh and blood,
and torture you to death?
Or do you want me to grovel on the ground
and beg you not to tell anyone
my real identity?
It is true that I tried to conceal
my identity from you.
Because I knew once I said it,
whatever between us...
would have to end this way.
So,
the important task you mentioned
actually refers to
shedding skin, replacing flesh,
renewing bones
and blood, and transforming the heart
in exchange for being reborn
and reincarnating as a human, right?
This approach is known to few.
I happen to
have read about it in an ancient book.
Does it mean
that you're done living as a War Demon
and now craving to become a human?
You War Demons have killed so many people.
Now that you've lost the battle,
you're seeking a new start
by secretly turning into a human?
What right do you have to do so?
I'm just a mediocre cultivator
at the Foundation Establishment Stage.
You might consider me inferior, Mr. Lu,
but I did slay War Demons
with this machete years ago!
Yes.
War Demons have committed
countless crimes.
You're a disciple of an immortal sect.
I am a remnant of the War Demons.
It's only reasonable
that you want to kill me.
But ask yourself this:
have I ever harmed you?
Have I ever hurt you?
All my senior brothers
died at the hands of your kind!
That makes all of you brutal animals!
But I am not.
You are no different.
You are no different!
Fine.
Take my life then.
♪ What do you think is ♪
♪ The most clumsy farewell ♪
♪ The endless slaughter and massacres ♪
♪ Do not wait until that thin snow
on the eaves ♪
♪ Turns a young man's hair white
before you regret it ♪
♪ When do you think ♪
♪ The bloody strife will come to an end? ♪
♪ End these everlasting battles ♪
Do it now.
♪ Holding the morning glow in hand,
I paint the world ♪
Or I'll be leaving then.
♪ Someone's got to clean up this mess ♪